Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Hatsune Miku
Arrangement: Hatsune Miku
Arranged by Miku Hatsune
This is the end of the video.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, things to go!
Should I get off...
Should I get off?
Um, well, yeah.
I was just about to get off...
Coroline...
Coroline's the one who gets off.
That's for sure.
Hey, we should get off.
Hey, we should get off...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This one doesn't stay either.
This one's not staying either.
This one's not gonna stay.
No more of this.
Exercise money.
That's great, isn't it?
You got a mike?
You're gonna shake it out?
We'll just have to live with the shaking.
I've taken some precautions for the width of the room.
But the shaking...
It shook just fine.
A little bit.
I'll do my best.
Yes, you can do it.
I think I can break it down there, too.
Well, thank you for your hard work.
Here we go.
I'm not hot in this costume anymore.
Indeed.
I'm happy.
I'm not happy anymore.
Are those tears?
Thirteen minutes.
Hold on a second.
Let's go.
Riko, Sakada, Myu.
That's our stage.
Let's go!
Looking forward to it!
Let's have fun!
Is the stage light?
Light?
Is it light?
Sunshine?
Not the sun?
Yes, sir.
All right, then.
Today, I'd like to invite all of you to make a partial appearance.
Let's have a round of applause for all of you.
Club together.
I'm looking for, I'm looking for, I'm looking for
Me.
If you put your hands together and blow, we'll say goodbye.
You'll find what you're looking for.
Tette-tete, tsurute-tete, tette-tete.
Tette-tete, telete-tete, telete-tete, my car looking for something big.
I'm looking for something big...
Tottottottottottottottottttttttttttttttttttttttttttttt...
Let's go look for it
Let's do it together.
Thank you.
Footsteps
Air Traffic
There's a lot of people here.
So many people.
It's a fun atmosphere.
Thank you very much.
From now on.
I'm going to go to a food stall.
I'd like to go
I'd like to go to a food stall.
Seino.
I'm going to eat it.
Is this it?
I have this at home.
You have it?
It's so good!
Bon appétit!
It's so cute.
Cute.
Delicious.
Amazing.
It's so cute.
It's so pretty.
Thank you. Thank you.
Can you dance a little?
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Footsie is in Malaysia.
They sell them in Malaysia.
That's right.
Bon appétit.
Okay, this sauce.
Okay, I'll have the barbecue sauce.
Bon appétit yakitori!
Bon appétit!
Amazing.
It's so spicy
If it gets really spicy
It's pretty spicy.
But it has a sour taste.
You can eat it with sofari
It's amazing!
Delicious!
Today's dish
I made it with this white soup stock.
Oita soy sauce.
Everyone's here.
I made these udon noodles.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
I use it at home.
Delicious.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
Delicious!
I love the sweet soup stock.
It's so good, I want some.
It smells so good.
Pork miso soup made with this is absolutely delicious!
We all made Graf's pork miso soup today!
I'm sure of it!
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit! Bon appétit!
Delicious!
I'm looking forward to it.
I may just do this all winter!
It's so good!
I want to eat it every day.
It's so cute on the outside!
Thank you very much.
I'll give it to you.
There's a forehead there.
From there?
Ready?
Go!
Ah!
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Se-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no
Okay.
Ah!
Thank you very much.
That sounded good.
Coming up on free throws now.
Yay.
We were just three of us.
We were making free throws.
It was difficult.
I made two, but I couldn't stop both times.
I stopped right away.
Congratulations.
I've done it before.
Come here.
That's great.
That's great. Good luck.
Yes, sir.
What's a googly ball?
What's a goyeball?
It's called "Oogi Balls.
It doesn't contain alcohol. It's very popular and many of our fans buy it.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit!
It's so good!
It's really delicious.
Bon appétit!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Would you like to grill it?
Would you like to try it?
I'll bake it.
Thank you very much.
Watch closely, ladies and gentlemen, your idol is going to bake.
You're all going to win.
Idol baking!
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It's good. It's good. It's good.
It's good.
What's the problem?
Heh.
I warmed it up.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's in there forever.
Soft drink.
Where are you?
We filmed at Fundoukin's factory.
They haven't exactly thrived since then.
Did something happen?
No, no, no... it's already happened.
Really?
First of all, he wanted to go see the factory.
To see how Batten Soy Sauce Soda actually operates.
and where Batten Soy Sauce Soda was actually made.
Of course, we received a lot of comments from our regular customers who use Fundokin.
We have received a lot of comments from them.
We are very grateful for that!
No, no, no, thank you very much!
You're absolutely right.
We've been using Fundou Kin's soy sauce
We've been using your soy sauce and your shop.
We use them on a regular basis.
But it's not often that we get to see the factory in person.
Don't you usually feel the same way?
Usually it's elementary school or social studies field trips.
We also give tours to the general public, but...
Yes, we do.
Yes, I do.
I think this is probably the first time
I think Batten Soy Sauce was the first to do this kind of filming.
Batten Soy Sauce is the first time I remember.
First! Oh! I'm so happy!
No one else has done it yet.
I appreciate it very much.
Thank you so much!
That's one of the reasons why we were chosen for the Friday Festival.
Thank you very much.
No, thank you very much.
We had another opportunity, didn't we?
Yes, we do.
Batten Soy Sauce.
I'd like you to support us.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
All the brains.
I'll see you later.
Yes, sir.
land
(in Japanese)
Sakura
Rino
Rie
This is our stage.
Let's go!
Location
Turn
Let's have fun.
From Sakimono.
Soy sauce.
I'm going to make it 2 or 2.5?
2.5? Today.
2.5.
Number 2, too.
One more time, starting with Rirua.
Yes.
Cheap.
Thank you for your patience.
Thank you for joining us.
Congratulations for being with us.
Congratulations.
Thank you for your hard work.
We will be in today's music video.
Of course we will be in the music video.
Mr. Fundokin's factory manager made an appearance on the Internet.
Mr. Fundoukin's factory manager appeared on the net, didn't he?
And this time, right?
We met the factory manager when we were walking around earlier.
Since we're here, let's talk about it.
The factory manager!
Here he is!
Pleased to meet you.
Thank you very much.
Very popular! Very popular!
Great!
Thank you very much!
You and Kosa made a strong appearance at the beginning of the song "Amaguchi Soy Sauce Tailoring".
It was a really nice filming at the factory, and we all had a great time dancing together.
Thank you very much.
For those of you who haven't seen it yet or haven't found it yet, I hope you will watch it again and again,
I hope you will watch it again and again to find it,
How do you like the real thing?
They were as kind as I had imagined.
Thank you very much for coming on stage.
Thank you all so much for coming today.
I am so happy that I am not here on this stage.
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. I was really a special guest Koshiencho.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
You have the loudest cheer of all of us today.
Mr. Higo. Mr. Higoroko.
Thank you for watching.
Exercise Kinki Gyosai is over!
We were also allowed to stand on the second floor stage, and there were two pretty tasty ones in between.
Basketball?
Yes, basketball and golf.
You just watched baseball. Did you really play golf?
Yes, I did play golf.
That's nice. I had a great time, and I even participated in the raffle at the end, and they gave me a present.
It was really fun.
It was a lot of fun. There were a lot of senior golfers there, and it was a very lively event.
I learned a lot.
It was great. I learned more and more about Fundoukin, not only soy sauce, but many other things as well,
I am sure you will see a lot of delicious food, so if you have a chance, I hope you will get some Fundoukin products as well,
We hope to see you again in the future.
I look forward to working with you again. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I want soybeans. And you, my dear. Sweet and tasty Fundoukin.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Replay. Replay.
I want soybeans. My love.
Dearly beloved.
He wrote, "Dearly beloved.
Say so.
Delicious.
Fundoukin is the best.
Thank you very much.